all right ladies and gentlemen today we
are going to be reviewing my $1 million
car collection last time we did this was
probably about a year ago and my car
collection at the time was $2 million
for 2.3
now one of my cars engulfs my whole
entire last car collection this car
collection is insane and we have a lot
of things that I want to show you let's
get into
it I feel right music SS with
[Music]
you so it's very obvious that I have two
bugs right behind me I have my first
Bugatti Chiron that I ever got and my
most recent Bugatti shiron pure Sports
One of 60 in the world but I actually
have a third bug and it's one of my
favorite bugs the beetle this is my
1969 Volkswagen Beetle this is a
original four-speed transmission manual
transmission and the original engine
everything on this car is original
except the tires cuz obviously I think
get changed as time goes on paint is
original this is like OG from back in
the day like there's barely any paint on
there yeah this is like you can tell at
this oh like you yeah this is like it
works perfect right if you ask me matter
of fact we still have the original
1969 Tire in the front but you guys that
don't know this right here is actually
the fuel tank so if you to put fuel you
have to open up your frunk because
supercars have frks clearly this is a
super car and has a frunk you take off
this cap and you put the fuel right into
there not going to lie took me a while
to find out my first time putting gas
into this
car She's a Beauty inside we have a
beautiful custom red interior obviously
this is not the original interior from
this car but it's literally just the
seats the
headliner Still Rock Solid metal for the
rust I have the dash that doesn't work F
section that doesn't work basically
nothing [__] works on it other than
the transmission and the engine which is
all we need to work I love driving this
car probably more than I like driving
70% of my cars one because it's manual
and two because it just feels good you
feel like you're in full control of the
car you're not going past 40 m hour but
I don't think you want to on this car
I'm going to be honest for some reason
since the day I bought this car and I've
had it for almost a year already that
peanuts has been there since I bought
the car and it has never fallen and I
don't ever want to take it off and I
feel like the previous owner liked
peanuts because right here the cup
holder is a peanut jar you know what's
ironic I'm allergic to
peanuts so if I touch that peanut I'm
probably [__] so the car did come with
some aftermarket very enhancing stickers
which gives this car a lot of horsepower
and and these stickers honestly have
every single one of them a very deep
meaning and truthfully keeps us safe
making our way to the back we've had to
do a custom Contraption sometimes here
and we always have to drive around with
this why because whenever it breaks down
we have to call our buddies or somebody
we hook it onto the car and we pull it
home there's no point of getting a tow
truck on this [__] we just pull it home
we never really drive it that far from
the house over here in the back area of
the vehicle never have a license plate
because for what's the point of that and
we have the license plate honk if Parts
fall off and we have been honked at and
parts have fallen off you can't open it
through the bar you have to like bend it
in a
way where you just force it to and then
it opens not right there that's a mean
[__] engine right there that [__] is
probably older than 90% of the people
watching this video so now we got done
with the first bug let's go into my
actual first bug that I've ever had my
pink Bugatti shiron I'm sure you seen
this car all over the place either doing
donuts riding around through the city or
interviewing a bunch of different
celebrities that we have done podcast
interviews inside of Bugatti this
Bugatti has been through a lot I can't
even lie so we have this key box where
all of the keys we're going to be
constantly pulling them out from here
and then we hired a professional key
catcher which we just throw in the box
and he catches this vehicle obviously is
not pink this is a wrap we ended up
wrapping it pink there's no real
explanation other than we don't give a
[__] we just said yo we got to look
different and we did it coming into the
inside of the Bugatti this [__] here had
uh the name of the person that built the
car his name was uh CH
Cristiano Ronaldo or something like
that interior of this car is obviously
on the classier side you feel like a
gentleman when you drive this car you
don't feel like you should be hauling
ass you feel like you should just be
cheating on your wife with your
girlfriend and you should be going to a
lowkey dinner and drinking some wine
that's what I feel and what I do when I
drive this car it honestly gives me a
great feeling and brings me pleasure one
of the cool features of the Chiron is
the speed key so for you to hit the max
speed on this vehicle you have to pull
out this speed key and then you have to
insert it into the air and unlock it
ironically the speed key opens up very
[__] slow which I don't understand
why that happens and I've actually never
used it I've never had a reason on why
to unlock the speed key cuz this sh's
already fast as it [__] is and again
this is my Bugatti to go cheat on my
wife and go have a chill classy dinner
if I want to holl ass I use my other
Bugatti that's what you got to have too
so interior wise obviously there's no
real carbon fiber in here this is not
really like a super sports spec what I
do like is that the key is matching on
the interior obviously it is on the
darker side now because it has some more
interior but the cool carbon fiber is on
the steering wheel which gives it a very
classy bi I really really really like it
but but you know I'm young I don't want
to feel like an old guy all the time now
you would expect for a car that's worth
$3 million for it to sound like an svj
super loud and epic but not really sound
like a bunch of
[Music]
turbos sounds good but it's not like a
wow the drive of this car is a big wow
effect I can't
[Music]
even it sounds cool cuz you hear the
turbos but it's not like a
I got all these crazy
svj which is going to be announced soon
making our way to the back of the
Bugatti we have this Wing right so this
Wing I personally love it not because of
the size of it because of what it does
because the size of that one is so much
more gangster this one I love because of
this right here and here we have the
seter forget brand and you might be like
bro why the [__] did you even put that
there you can never even see it yeah you
can only see it when I'm hauling ass by
you at 180 mph and I let go of the
accelerator and this Wing will catapult
forward it would literally like and when
it goes forward these compressors bring
it up and then this Wing you will
literally see it flat like this like
completely flat and you'll just see
setup for get huge that's a [__]
Flex Jesus bro you pay these guys
minimum wage $80 an hour and they
[__] can't do anything right now
keyman have that now you'd expect that
I'm paying six million [__] dollars
for my buatti Shear on pure sport you
would expect a big iconic key I would
expect some [__] the size of my [__]
nut is huge like that but
no I paid $6
million for a [__] old swagon key but
you know
what
my my standard of a flip key is slow
from the Bugatti Chiron speed key now
this Bugatti shiron pure for key moves
very fast right that's that's that's a
plus yes me right that's that's dou now
obviously this is not the key that I was
given with the car I lost the original
key and the original key is $225,000 and
I don't want to pay $25,000 for the
original key so I'm riding around with
the spare key monthly payment on this is
$70,000 monthly payment on this is
$50,000 so you're looking at $130 but
add a stupid [__] key I'm at 150 on
just these two cars I'm good I I'm I'm
I'm a I'm smarter than that I make smart
business decisions I would never spend
money unnecessarily I would never do
that now obviously this color is
absolutely beautiful purple just just
look at the front of these cars man that
is you if that and this is the guy that
tell you not to worry about there's a
very big [__] difference Tyrone
Bugatti making our way to our Bugatti
shiram pure sport now this is obviously
super cool but now we're at a different
[__] level here boys just getting
side of here obviously the interior is
similar in design but now on the actual
spec it is very very very different the
last one say is a Shear on here this has
the Bugatti logo there's leather
everywhere on the other car this says
alcantra we have the moon roof which the
moon roof is super sick only for
pictures because when you're driving the
sun is beaming through your head and
it's burning perod I told you luckily
there's a little bit of so that helps
when you make your way inside of here
like look at the amount of carbon on the
dash literally the whole entire Dash
this carbon fiber all through here it's
one big piece the details on the doors
of the Bugatti emblem or whatever the
[__] that is it looks super sick then we
have the carbon fiber in the bottom
section over here now the only thing
that I do complain about this car is
that I paid $3 million more for this car
so a $6 million Bugatti and I would
expect for chairs to recline forward and
backwards so I'm literally clicking this
and no how do you move your chair
forward and backward with a [__]
railing what the [__] you pay $6 million
for a coin you have to adjust it like if
this was a Toyota Corolla so if you're
driving a Toyota Corolla right now or a
Nissan Ultima and you're adjusting your
chair like this well guess what we're on
the same level and if you're in a Toto
Corolla in a Nissan Tima and you're
adjusting your chair
electronically you have just beaten me
you won now the big difference is the
paddles I love the paddles on this one
because is they're a lot bigger and
they're a lot sportier they look like
the GT3 RS paddles the other paddles are
honestly kind of pathetic they look like
plasticky and they're L smaller this is
definitely the next level Bugatti and
they drive very similar this will feel
is a little bit more planted but I don't
know if it's just personal but this one
does not sound as nice as that one that
one sounds nicer this one drives better
that one is faster this one looks more
aggressive so you got to have both it's
a good balance now the sound in the
start is going to be very similar to
that one but when you're driving and
you're [__] with the turbos it sounds
different I know I know the car
enthusiasts out there like bro it's a
cold start you just turned it on and
you're already revving it yeah who gives
a [__] man this [__] has warranty so
we'll be fine anything that happens
we're good my favorite part about this
car is the back of this car oh key key
Guy come on key Guy come on come on
there you go [__] we got to be quick on
these guys man cuz if not you got to hit
him with surprise bro so the back of
this car is by far 10 times more
aggressive than this car it makes that
car look like a child Bugatti come on
Bugatti come on oh that didn't sound
good that did not sound good this just
obviously sexy I love how they actually
color match the interior specs like the
details inside with the actual engines
cover which is beautiful this pushes the
exact same horsepower they're both W6
15600 horsepower this one's just slower
because of this Wing the downforce that
this spring does is what makes it slore
which it's fine it's a couple miles per
hour at the end of the day if I'm going
300 M hour and you're going 305 we're
both hauling has so now that we got
through the bugs we're going to now move
over to our GT3 RS 992 whc package 2024
this is a 307 sticker this is almost a
full Max spec and truthfully this is one
of my favorite portions that I've had so
far and I want you guys to let me know
what is your favorite in all of these
cars in order so drop a comment Down
Below on which car you love the most and
which car you love the least and trust
me my favorite car are not the Bugattis
moving out over here to the Porsche GT3
RS this is my second GT3 at had a GT3 92
six-speed manual which we blew the
transmission two times and burned the
clutch once good thing we had dealer
warranty on that as well and that was
covered now this one is nap manual we
got rid of that Porsche because we put
about 10,000 mies into it and we're just
ready to move on and this is the daddy
of that every single car I get just
engulfs every single car now big con
from this car is that it is not manual
the pdk is cool but I just love popping
the clutch randomly for no reason we
have the custom decal on the side of set
and forget so obviously that's supposed
to say GT3 RS but I feel like that's
pretty standard and basic and I'm no
basic [__] clearly inside of the GT3 RS
our very uncomfortable y SEC seats
obviously key guide come on there you go
hey h he's getting the hanger finally
inside we have our color matching yellow
key and these very uncomfortable seats
they're very hard obviously as everybody
should know and I'm sure they are aware
and it has the matching seat belts with
the exterior we have the extra yellow
rim on the speedometer which I think
that's a $3,000 spec and the $3,000
yellow rim on the clock which the clock
is never [__] used aside from that we
have yellow stitching inside of the car
yellow numbers on top of here yellow
stitching on the steering wheel yellow
stitching on the paddle shifters this is
a perfect black and yellow spec with
Khalifa would be very happy and very
proud of this car this car currently is
stock so the sound of it isn't the
sexiest we will have an exhaust coming
for it very soon I just haven't wanted
to take it to the shop and leave it
there because I don't want the car to be
down 2 3 weeks cuz I don't sound like I
don't have other cars to drive right now
here on the door you would expect if you
spend half a million dollars on a car
you would get a real door knob to open
the door and no get this little ribbon
so you can just pull it and you actually
open the door it's kind of cool you get
used to it to over time but that as well
you have the yellow stitching all
throughout the top all throughout the
bottom and this pretty cool carbon fiber
handle which is an add-on feature as
well this you3 RS logo as well it's
super cool honestly I love this car as a
whole but let's get a little cold start
to see how it
sounds obviously it doesn't sound crazy
and I'm not able to Red Line cuz when
this car red lines I'll tell you right
now this thing sounds crazy I've done
Donuts in this around that Bugatti and
around that Bugatti in an eight in a
figure 8 and this thing handles
[Music]
beauti over here on the top of the car
we have the carbon fiber roof spec which
is super super cool and then what the
[__] are these for bro these are for
like down Force right canards but
whatever the point is I drift the [__]
out this [__] I do donuts around the
both of the Bugattis in a figure eight
like a boss with no clutch and I might
be the first guy that converts this to
manual that's going to be crazy mov went
to the back of the vehicle we have
obviously the big ass sexy Wing this is
the most recognizable feature of the GT3
RS which is the super big Wing I love it
I never really use the DRS downforce
whenever you click it this makes its way
up click it makes it way down and you
actually feel the difference which is
the crazy part you actually feel the car
going from having down forest rather
than not it's pretty cool feature aside
from that stock these cars do shoot
Flames we have multiple clips of this
car as we're doing donuts shooting FL
out of the rear exhaust fully stock so I
can imagine with an exhaust and a nice
tune little flame map [__] with the
settings big Flames like that
[Music]
come soon another thing is I'm usually
typically used to a frunk on these cars
because my other GT3 had one this thing
does not have a frunk It Is non-existent
Us in the front is the intercooler so
this is what cools the car so you can be
able to abuse it for a long periods of
times on the track and telling you right
now that has come very handy for the
stuff we've done to this car key guy key
guy oh this guy's getting fast all right
moving our way now to my C7 Z6 boy boy
you guys are not ready for this thing oh
I forgot this is worth about
$400,000 this is worth about
$70,000 and this [__] is a beast this is
my
2019 Corvette C7 Z06 procharged this
[__] has a turbo the size of my
[__] nut humongous wait to you
the left one or the right one this is
this is the left one now my right one is
not as big we're working on that my left
one is ginormous don't mind these cars
are are very dusty I know they are very
dirty we just did this video
spontaneously we have construction going
on here in the house let me let me move
this John forward so obviously this is a
s-speed manual transmission z7
Z6 I'm just going to let the noise do
the talking
[Music]
this thing sounds absolutely
beautiful oh my God this this car is
music to my ears and I love that it's
manual in the back you hear the
beautiful V8 and in the front you hear
my left nut my ginormous
ProCharger is a beautiful beautiful
sounding car this thing is pushing a
little over 1,300 horsepower and this is
actually my drift car which is kind of
crazy right why would you get a car
that's 1,300 horsepower to do drifting
because why not now there's a con to
this car this car does not have warranty
it does not have anything and uh we take
care of it very very very dearly because
it spends 90% of its time in the shop
like the car that I wish I could be
adding to this tour which is my Nissan
sky Skyline R34 currently in the shop
we're tuning it up making it actually
sound like a real 2JZ which would
probably be right behind this car but
it's currently in the shop we actually
went to Japan to go buy this car in
person we saw four different ones we
liked the one that we got we bought it
and then we waited for it to get on the
shipment port and then we came back to
Miami waited for a month and now it's
here so that's a very cool experience on
what we did buying that car actually in
Japan so people were like you didn't
have to fly there for that well I
[__] wanted to if you have the
opportunity to do crazy stuff like that
why not do it I have three other cars at
the shop that I don't really want to
talk about just yet because they'll
probably be in the shop for a little bit
longer maybe another month or two that's
a long time for me so once I actually
get them
back so like we were saying uh this
interior is not the cleanest but
honestly this is a what I like to call a
project car so you can kind of get away
with having khaki interior in the back
we have our drift set up so these are
our tires that we use to smoke you just
smoke these tires they're cheap they're
like 100 bucks you a couple donuts below
them change them in and out we have a
bunch of different sets and in the front
we have very nice radios when you drift
and you do donuts you need very good
grip in the front over to the back
obviously this [__] can never have a
plate because with this we are never
stopping and there's not one moment
we're doing something remotely legal on
this car when we drive this car so that
being said let's now move on to our
McLaren
720s all right so there's a long story
behind this key right here this is
actually the McLaren key I take full
responsibility this is a novatech whole
entire spec with a beautiful history of
curb rash and the speed bumps this car
is I think every person's every Trader's
dream which is to actually own a McLaren
because the doors go up they sound crazy
they're fast they feel really good to
drive this feels better to drive than
the pink Bugatti Chiron for some odd
reason I don't know why this car just
feels really good to drive I did a
custom steering wheel on this one so we
made all this carbon fiber and it has a
better grip inside of it it's like every
other McLaren we have a matching yellow
spec with the interior just as we have
with the Porsche when I saw this I'm
like oh I have to get it they're
literally like brothers you have yellow
black and yellow GT3 RS black and yellow
McLaren 720s they kind of sound similar
that's why they're the brght other
whenever I want to go fast shoot flames
and Pop I drive this whenever I want to
do donuts and do degenerous [__] and
really tap into the car Community I use
that aside from the key not working this
one is pretty reliable I've had three
McLarens I had a 570s I had a 720s and
this is my second 720s and the first two
were not so reliable this one is it's
kind of a hit or miss with these cars
you can never really kind of rely on
McLaren but you know I don't really want
to talk about it too much because it has
been treating me very well I don't drive
it as much I probably drive it maybe
once or twice every other week but it
has been getting the job done getting me
from point A to point B shooting flames
and going fast as [__] sucks I can't
turn this car on for you guys cuz this
car sounds really cool the key was
working yesterday but we did some custom
Contraption in order for it to work but
I'll show you guys the rear end of this
car rear end of this car looks extra
aggressive because we have obviously the
novatech full body kits novatech exhaust
and our custom license plates on every
single car because here in Miami you
don't need to have license plates if
you're a [__] balla oh my God and I'm
not there yet I think I have more to go
so I'm kind kind of forcing myself to
categorize myself as a volume I have LIC
aside from that this car is very [__]
low like literally a finger like not
like not not even a finger fits through
here this car is extremely low to the
ground and it still somehow rides good
but there is a big con to this car being
this slow I I I I'm going to be honest
guys if you see online one of my cars
don't buy it don't don't don't do it if
you see a car of mine online or a girl
of mine online don't don't do it I don't
recommend it it's been very well tested
this is literally completely falling
apart because we just don't give a [__]
I can pull up into an entrance of a
shopping center and raise it and I
choose not to why because I like the
sound of the script and I I like same
people
like and I'm in there like yep it
doesn't matter so McLaren 720s is
definitely awesome now moving over to
our Rolls-Royce cullin mansuy wide body
okay guys this is a one of one spec I
had a Manser G wagon which I just got
rid of ironically but I just have too
many [__] cars honestly I don't need
more dailies for daily for daily so I
got rid of it this is 10 times better
than the G wagon the G wagon looked cool
cool but this one looks cool and feels
cool you have the glow-in-the-dark
rollsroyce emblem here at the front this
is a wrap this is a gray wrap with
chrome deleted whole entire front end we
have the full carbon fiber manery kits
all over the front we have these super
thick rims along with the full manery
kit and the wide body the wide body
makes this look like a completely
different car moving over to the inside
we have a stunning Orange in interior a
real orange interior there some dull
oranges in inside of some cullins this
is that bright Miami livid orange which
I love best part is when you're inside
of this it's a real Manser kit I don't
think this is a fake kit I would hope
not because then I got scammed that
would [__] suck but this car feels
good you you touch it you could tell
it's not Chinese what I love is that we
do have the full orange sunroof as well
because some of these cars they have the
whole entire orange kit but they have a
black roof and they don't have The
Starlights we have star lights and we
have the orange Roofing as well this car
honestly is just a big boss car I love
it I daily I put a [__] ton of miles on
this car I drive it every single day and
uh I don't have it with the darkest
tints because I like how the orange
looks when you look from the outside in
usually I used to be the guy with 0%
tints everywhere I don't want you to see
inside but now I'm at the point where I
love the Cosmetic look that it gives so
I say that this is one of one because it
literally stays here on the door and
honestly I've never seen another one
like this so this is very clearly one of
one to me went our way to the back of
the car very standard I had a ghost Don
cullinan and a phantom so I've had five
Rose rses I think I've hit the max I
think the next I I have is a maner
phantom and honestly like I don't know
where to go maybe I'll just sell all
these cars and just move to a [__]
Island and just reset I don't know
because like I'm literally like Max now
on the possibility of going to the next
level every single time and each level
gets harder which I like it because it
challenged me to continuously get better
and something that many would not expect
from this is that this [__] has an
exhaust this Cullen has an exhaust it's
does it actually sounds nice
[Applause]
look it sounds better when it's warm I I
shouldn't even be reving it if it's not
warm right but who cares moving over to
the back we have the maner wing and Wing
as well as our custom license plate
which is absolutely beautiful key gu all
right moving out aside from this now we
have my mayback Sprinter van so I've had
this car for I think this is the only
car that's stood the test time this
thing has been around for almost 2 years
now this has been around for a very long
time but I love this car this obviously
a car to be driven in I never really
drive this car I drive it sometimes when
the truck is on we have a truck that's
in the shop right now we just throw [__]
in here and this is our truck we just
throw stuff in here and this car is the
ultimate Flex to be driven around if you
want to get somebody picked up from the
airport some one of your friends they
get picked up in here plenty of space
for luggage you have the curtains which
come down you have the TV that you could
have them watching whatever they want to
be watching these seats reclin back and
forward speakers in here are crazy
ambient lighting this is like a mobile
executive office as well because we
could
bring this area up bring the trays this
is my mayback man that's pretty much it
there's nothing really else to it I've
had this car for about to be two years
now and I tried to get rid of it but
then I said you know what [__] it I
don't there's no need for it I it's paid
off majority of these cars are paid off
there's no reason for me to get rid of
it it actually has some type of utility
these other cars some of them don't have
utility this one actually gets us them I
want to talk to the driver in the front
come here pick the phone button but yo
drop off the girlfriend pick up the wife
going to dinner something that I do wish
I had with this car was the matching
front the front is pretty basic it's
black this doesn't have the blue seats
so if you drive me around you're not in
the blue seats sorry I drive I don't
really care like you know we drive this
[__] when the front tires have no tire
that's how you know we really drive this
and we put a lot of time and miles into
it we changed the headlights from the
last time we did this video the last
headlights that we had were ugly so we
changed it to more updated version of
the mayback headlights so as we go
through this maze here of cars we're
going to walk over to a car that I
didn't really buy a car that I was kind
of just handed by life I guess this is
Jordan's old Miata so Jordan is a friend
of mine that passed away due to cancer
he was friend business partner and we
did a lot of stuff together so Jordan
went to Arizona for this treatment and
as he's over there in Arizona he he
hadn't walked for like 6 7even months he
took his McLaren up there with him and
he just wanted to sell it so he's like
bro List It Up on Marketplace sell it he
paid $1,000 for it because this has a
turbo sticking out of the hood which is
super cool it's manual this is a
full-blown drift car and he was like yo
just sell the car and whatever you can
get for it sell it we had it online
probably for a week or two no hits he's
like look bro I don't really need the
money if you want to keep it you you
guys can keep it if nobody comes and
buys it so we decided you know what
after his passing nobody hit us up to
buy it it's been a very long time since
this is a very unique car and not
everybody really wants to buy it so I
decided to keep it myself we have taken
care of his girlfriend we've taken care
of his family we've given them plenty of
stuff that have helped them out so we
decided to stay with this car is my
memory of Jordan and we're going to kind
of just build it and have it as our own
car here forever there's no reason for
me to ever sell this car there's a sent
mental meaning behind this car
and yeah I mean it just kind of reminds
me of him and all the great times that
we had inside this car and truthfully
there's no price tag to this car at all
and me selling it I know he wouldn't
want that because it would go to
somebody else and to do who knows what
with it I know it's going to be in good
hands with me and I'm going to be taking
care of so oh and moving on now to
what's right next to it which is
obviously massive is my command unit
shout out to S1 Security Group for
helping me out with this I I have 24/7
security here at the house and so
they're not in and out of the house and
I don't kind of have a room in there and
the dog isn't you know interrupting
whenever they have changes in shifts
they go inside of the command units and
they just change shifts they're looking
at the cameras connected to the house
they have a bathroom in there they can
eat in there basically it's a mobile
office and they can do whatever they
want inside of that truck so they're not
connecting to the house and they make
sure that the house is secure all right
now that we're over here on one of the
sides of my house here we have my two
other vehicles which I don't think I've
ever really used and I don't think I
will ever really use them which is my
10m Maverick X3 this is basically the
biggest baddest off terrain vehicle you
could possibly have we have it with
light bar sound system everything tow
hitch in the front just in case we get
stuck i' probably driven this thing
realistically like four or five times I
got it cuz I got a really good deal on
it least I thought I did and I probably
used it one time for a video and then I
completely forgot about it there's my
dog security dog
I can get him to [__] [__] you up
right now bro just one command and this
is [__] you
up this is my jet ski scooter scooer is
what they call it we really just bought
this for one
video after that one video we kind of
just forgot about it because it never
really turned back on we threw it inside
the pool and it just died and it's just
here it's kind of like the graveyard
section of the house and last but not
least definitely not least is
Sebastian's Corvette C7 and his Mercedes
S550 so this is Sebastian The Man Behind
this camera's cars I gifted him both of
these cars for what was I think it was
your birthday right my birthday was 6
months ago and I've only had those cars
for three months I don't think it's I
think I just gave them to you randomly
because you were doing a great job yeah
see that's that's a good job this
[__] keyman isn't getting
anything take that for example
keyman Jes this is Seas Corvette
C7 and as well it is a seven-speed
manual this interior is actually nicer
than mine because it's black mine is
that ugly khaki and tear and he shreds
this sh SE did not know how to drift and
he learned how to drift inside of this
which is pretty cool this is his S550
which his S550 was not like this I give
it to him differently he decided to give
it his own custom touch which I'm all
for cuz it looks very different and
unique I give you a car and look at it
you how long has this been like this but
at least you have the nice white
interior which is well need some TLC
it's pretty much it and definitely the
least cars these cars that's my wife and
that's my girlfriend's car they just
don't know
it so ladies and gentlemen this is my $1
million car collection we are missing
three other cars and we will update that
as soon as we get them back might do
another car collection make sure you
guys hit that like And subscribe button
thank you for
watching oh oh oh and by the way I own a
boat I just don't have it here it's on
the water pop up some B in my boat which
I
[Music]
love by the way I think you're missing
more than three cars I think so too
right [__] how can you forget because we
[__] said him forget
[Music]
[__] well the video was supposed to
end [__] on a high note nice chill Vibe
b beach good music but we felt like we
had to let you guys know what happened
to one of my favorite cars in the
fleet yo it's on fire i c fire now my V
just this history on the good side this
sh going to go viral on Instagram it's
not a car anymore yeah we definitely set
and forget a littleit too hard there but
this was the C7 Z06 that I told you guys
that I had so much planned for it it was
my drift car it was in the shop for
months I barely driven it the one day
that it finished and that I actually got
to drive it it flew the [__] up we're
doing regular casual Donuts as we always
do on a live stream coincidentally
enough something blew I think it was
personally a fuel line cuz the same
exact thing happened with my pink Lambo
when I caught fire but luckily somebody
was there on the spot quick and they
were able to extinguish it and take it
out this caught fire and we had two fire
extinguishers on scene which are these
two right here which we literally used
and it did nothing I guess what what's
made out of sales this fiberglass right
fiber don't touch it if I were you oh
[__] why now you're going to be itching
for the rest of the day yeah yeah [__]
don't do that either why you're going to
be itchy there no but I'm wearing a
shirt the shirt's going to get itchy
well the point is that I guess
fiberglass is very flammable we emptied
out both of those tanks and it did
nothing it took fire rescue probably 20
minutes to show up cuz we were you know
doing donut like at 1: 2 in the morning
and I guess these homies were knocked
out they were sleeping or they didn't
give a [__] cuz they took their sweet
ass time to pull up by the time they
pulled up the whole thing caught fire
they did manage to save somewhat of this
rim and a little bit of the rear end
aside from that every everything else is
gone look bro look at this like I know
this [__] got hot cuz obviously the
whole thing caught fire but I would
never expect for the heat to melt the
rim like it literally melted through
these rims these are $2,000 racing
wheels I would expect that they're able
to withstand the Heat and yeah my
Corvette's now gone so what other drift
car should I get now cuz I need a drift
car or in my fleet I feel empty without
one I thought that was the whole point
of that oh oh yeah well we we got to we
got to show them what we got going on
here so I'm putting this behind this so
I told you guys that we were shipping
the R34 to Miami and it's been in the
shop since it got here now she's finally
at the shop which is right here so this
is kind of crazy how like when it got
here I'm like yo I bought this [__] in
Japan I was doing donuts in Japan I was
drifting it in Japan having a crazy time
in Japan and now it came here to Miami
felt like I don't know it just feels
like I don't know it's kind of weird how
you can just have money and do whatever
the [__] you want like imagine going to
a completely different country on the
other side of the world and you just
bring it over here just cool to me so I
was going to use this as my drift car
but truthfully I don't want to do that
because I've already got two cars on
fire this car that CAU fire I'm taking a
probably like a 70 $80,000 loss on that
car because I I'm not going to claim
into the insurance one because they're
going to see that I was doing donuts and
two they probably dropped me from the
insurance since the lambo caught fire
they did pay me out on that I did lose
some money on that but I don't want to
get flagged as a highrisk client and
then them completely remove me and I
can't ensure my Bugatti and my 10 other
cars you know so I'm just going to take
that to the chin charge it to the game
take the L and I'm going to take care of
this girl right here thing is [__]
beautiful and now we need a new drift
car so what drift car should we get and
please please let it not be flammable
please so we decided to give you guys
the latest update on the car tour which
is the Corvette on fire GTR out of the
shop and we still have three cars that
are on the way so stay tuned for the
next car tour video make sure to like
comment and subscribe and I'll see you
boys in the next
[Music]
one I wonder if you know who in Tokyo if
you seen it and you mean it then you
know you have to go
[Music]
oh